

Pedro Pereira Frontend Dev.

+351 919 300 228 pedromcdp@gmail.com github.com/pedromcdp

About Me

My name is Pedro Miguel Pereira, I'm 25 years old, I live in the city of Aveiro and I have a Master's degree in Communication and Web Technologies from the University of Aveiro. From a very young age I've been curious about technology and what it offers to our lives, which has led me to get interested in application development, with a special focus on web development. I'm motivated, committed, and I enjoy collaborating with others, exchanging ideas with coworkers, and I always give my best in every project I'm involved in. Im also fluent in both Portuguese and English.

Experience

Research Grant -Augmanity Frontend

University Of Aveiro October 2022 - July 2023

Curricular Internship Usability & User Experience

Altice Labs - Aveiro May 2020 - July 2020

Academic Internship Web Developer

Decimal Informática e Gestão, Lda -October 2022 - July 2023

"iHelp" iOS Application Professional Aptitude

Project

Aveiro 2016

Responsible for developing the frontend of a web platform focused on workforce engagement using React;

Selection of technologies for the platform; Integration of the frontend with a .NET API.; Documentation of the solutions developed.

Needs and requirements analysis;

Technological analysis associated with the component;

Development of the Angular component;

Usability tests.

Responsible for maintaining and updating content on the company's various websites;

Maintenance of the company's online shop;

Development of an application in C#.

Conducted Market Analysis;

Designed the entire user experience and user interface;

Developed the iOS application using Objective-C;

Presentation of the application at the Escola Secundária José Estêvão & Catholic University of Porto.

Git

Docker

Master's In Communication And Web Technologies

University Of Aveiro

2021-2023

Degree in Multimedia Communication

Polytechnic Institute Of Guarda

2017-2020

Professional Course For Computer Systems Management And Programming **Technicians**

Escola Secundária José Estêvão

2013-2016

Skills

Education

JavaScript Next.Js **Tupescript** Node.Js React **Express** MongoDB **TailwindCSS React Native**